How to help
Helping out is very easy once you understand the basics. We have full tutorials available on our website, as well as video tutorials: airportediting.com

We highly recommend you join our Slack team - it's a great way to meet other editors and get tips and tricks! Email mailto:contact@airportediting.com to get started.

It's furthermore highly recommended to check out our Infinite Flight Airport Editing Beginner's Guide where you will find information on all challenges of Airport Editing, starting with joining and setting up the software to the actual editing process.

What to do / not to do
The general rule is "draw what you see", with a few exceptions:

DO

Use accurate imagery for airports.
Add taxiways.
Add taxiway lines.
Add parking spots.
Modify runways.
Add airport boundaries.
Add airport ATC frequencies (please see websites such as airnav.com for this).
DON'T

Add runway markings or text/numbers with taxiway lines (this includes runway numbers, blast pad arrows, etc.).
Create jet bridges using the taxiway tool.
Forget to include a boundary.
Make up an airport - it HAS to be a real airport.
Outline buildings with a taxi line.
Airport accuracy
In order to achieve maximum accuracy for each airport (in terms of features drawn, location and sizing), the majority of our editors use SASPlanet (for Windows and Linux only) and WED-O-Maker. This allows for detailed satellite imagery to be shown on WED. It's free to use, and easy to set up (tutorials are available on the WED-O-Maker website).

One last thing...
We appreciate every contribution that is made! Thank you very much to each person that contributes, you are really helping to make the Infinite Flight world a better place. 

Airport editing run by Cameron Carmichael Alonso (@carmichaelalonso), Jonathan Perkins (@jpperks) and David Cutler (@davidcutler). 

Note: by submitting anything to this project, you are bound by the Contributor License Agreement.